Yeah.
Now that I know where to find Dolan, I should be on my way.
Wait.
If that device lets you see the unseen out of the way errand, I'm asking you to help me.
A lawyer.
I need to know who killed IRSA.
Why should you have justice and not me?
Look, I'll head for Red Rich pass where Irs's body was found and wait for you there.
A few minutes of your focus is all I need.
Don't make me beg.
Yeah,
Mhm.
Yeah.
Progress.
Thanks.
E.
We really, really, really
never know when I might need thes.
Yeah,
Just getting mad,
Okay.
Showing you that way.
His
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah,
son.
Save your energy.
Yeah.
Oh!
Oh,
no,
I can't spare the weight.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Tasty.
This is what you intend.
Bring these ancient things back to life.
Their power serves us machine demons from beneath the ground.
It's a nightmare.
Nightmares?
Yes.
The worst dreams of our enemies come true.
Yeah,
first
you could
Mhm.
Uh huh.
So much for catching him alone.
Thes things will destroy us all.
They will only destroy our enemies and bring us back the lands that working
way may have intruders.
Forgive this intrusion Alloy, You left me no choice.
Who is this?
An interested party.
Now the focus is air disabled.
But I don't know for how long.
The rest is up to you.
Who is this
off?
Okay,
okay.
Construction
these days
nor a girl lives
kill her.
No.
You had your chase?
Yeah,
My mother?
Yeah.
Tonight, I think.
Yes,
that's coming back.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Just think about that.
It's
this time.
Yeah,
it's
Yeah.
Yeah,
you know?
Yeah.
Snap.
Okay.
You were just
Yeah,
e
It's
you know,
God
e back.
Okay.
State so
mhm.
Yeah,
that's right.
No one here,
Thomas.
Yeah,
All already?
I promise.
I'll tell you everything.
The killers who came from me The proving Who are they?
The eclipse.
Some kind of holy warriors.
A cult of the Shadow Kharja, Shadow Kharja.
Except they're not like any Karger I've known.
They don't pray to the sun.
They worship some kind of devil.
I'm not interested in their superstitions.
Oh, it's not a superstition there, devil!
Israel!
It has a name.
Ah, voice.
And you've heard it speak steel to my soul.
I heard just once when it saw you such a voice.
Cold, awful jangle.
It scrapes your bones, the Hollows, your guts, a metal sound.
But like nothing dug from the earth or smelted in a forge.
Haiti's That's what they call it Haiti's.
And what did it say?
System threat detected just three words.
The eclipse were sent to kill me because I look like another woman.
Older, maybe twice my age.
Short hair.
Who is she?
I don't know.
My focus found her image.
Once I had taken a delve near makers end, there was a door beside it, a kind of ancient device that contained the woman's image.
My focus recorded the location.
When I surfaced, they were waiting.
I left when I saw the priest, but then he showed me Hell is's encouragement.
I didn't laugh after that.
They gave me a focus toe.
Watch my every move.
I followed orders.
Why you?
I was a scrounge er a row.
Mature in dark places.
Good at what I do.
I suppose they knew I would serve them well as a scout.
What are these Eclipse cultists after?
Besides me, they never said.
But given the carriages civil war, they must want to overthrow some king of art and take Meridian back.
Why didn't they get to a VOD through you?
Too much dirt under my nails for an audience with one true son King.
But whatever er saw, Aaron told me.
Theis clips heard every word through my focus.
That's why I couldn't warn you if I tried.
They would have killed my family
when they attacked the proving a man came from me.
Tall, strong, dead eyes he lifts.
And who is he?
The terror of the sun stacker off corpses We Ostrom called him when he was a mad something's champion.
If only he died with his king.
But now he leads the eclipse.
I tell you, he's the most dangerous man alive.
Why are the eclipse digging up ancient machines, and how did they get them toe work?
I thought they wanted them for scrap, but they brought them back to life, plugged some kind of device into the corpses so that Haiti's could whisper to them and call them from their grave.
I thought that kind of machine before are there others much bigger, bristling with ancient weapons, those they call death bring er's.
I've only seen them buried in the ground.
But after today, anything is possible.
Sounds to me like they're raising an army.
If so, the world will fall.
And I helped dig the pit.
I've heard enough.
I won't beg for my life.
But if there's any mercy in you free my family, please.
Where would I find them?
My focus recorded the location.
There are always guards there.
You look like you can handle yourself.
You're
your role in events was coursed.
Perhaps you're not an evil man.
Just a week One I am.
The only strength I ever found in this life was my family.
It will take many good deeds to make up for the crimes you've committed.
You're sparing me.
After all I've done yes.
Forge a new life, Dolan.
One of better make.
Then the rest of my life will be lived in your debt.
Go to the place where your family is being held and wait for me.
We'll make their lives the first ones you save.
I didn't earn this mercy, but I will die to make myself worthy of it.
I will be waiting for you.
Mhm.
Thank you.
Uh huh.
Uh huh,
Mm.
Yeah.
Sorry.
What?
Okay,
it's errand.
He's in trouble.
Think about Okay.
Okay.
Yeah,
progress.
That.
All right
around.
Di General.
I'm glad that's over with.
Thanks for the help.
Come on over here and have a word.
Can't be too prepared to Come on.
What are you waiting for?
What are you doing out here all alone?
Where are your men?
I'm not going to risk their lives.
I don't mind putting my worthless ass on the line, but not theirs.
Sorry I had to drag you into it.
Don't worry.
This is just a knave.
Ridge Day for May.
You know, take down some machines, tracks, um, killers.
Right.
I'd hate to see a busy morning for you.
Ready to get started.
Are you sure you're all right?
Well, I'm sober, so No.
Well, I'm glad you're thinking straight.
At least don't get used to it.
Tell me exactly what happened to IRSA.
Start from the beginning.
No one knows for sure.
She left in the middle of the night with a few of her best man, her best men.
But she didn't bring you.
No, I've been drinking a lot.
Maybe she sudden goddamn, I don't know I couldn't hack it.
Search parties found their bodies the next day and the corpses of some shadow carjacked cowards.
It was an ambush.
Shadow Carter Animals.
They beat her so bad we can't even show her face before burial.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, when I find the soldiers who did this, they'll be sorry to You don't have any idea why she left in the middle of the night?
No, but it must have been urgent.
A message of reporters, Some new shadow card.
Your threat?
I don't know.
Why would the shadow card to do this?
Because they hate us and Earth's.
And most of all, she teamed up with a VOD to kick their ass is out of Meridian.
They've been licking their wounds for two years.
But you finally found a way to get back at her.
All right.
Show me where Cfl and I'll do what I can to help.
Come on, follow me.
Why would ever so come all the way out here?
I don't know.
It doesn't make sense.
Is this shadow Kharja territory?
No.
They broke the ceasefire as soon as they set foot in the Clift.
Almost there.
All right.
This is it.
Where the ambush happened.
Our soldiers have been over it, but maybe that fancy artifact of yours can find a clue or something.
Please.
I need to find the bastards that did this.
A shadow card, your spirit.
There must be shot of cardio armor,
Right?
Please look like drag marks.
Those bloodstains.
Not the kind of a pool around a corpse
arrow scattered there.
They look like smears.
It's perfectly sure never seen action.
Strange going to scratch on it.
I looked at his new never fired.
Yeah.
Did someone move your body through here?
What do you see there?
This stain forms a line as if blood dripped off the edge of something like a cart.
See?
Car tracks.
I think someone moved the bodies here, then scattered them across the field.
Wait, Are you saying that dead found here were killed somewhere else?
But why would the Shadow card should do that?
At this point?
I'm not taking it for granted that the Shadow Kharja responsible.
Of course they were.
Well, let's follow these tracks and find out.
No!
Okay,
I get why they wanted Ursa dead wife.
Facon Ambush!
There's more to this and we're gonna figure it out.
And
okay,
Thes guys aren't Shadow Kharja.
They're from my tribe.
The Assaraf.
Is this how your people usually greet each other?
Incoming!
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Your position
finished?
Oh,
what?
I think it's calling in machines.
Get ready.
Yeah.
Ravage er weakness to fire.
Strong against Chuck.
Freeze canister Power cell Ravage your cannon.
Destroying these components disables ravage your canon attacks.
This heavy weapon can be picked up and used after it has been detached from the machine
I liberated.
Oh, cases.
It's
Yeah,
right.
Oh,
very good.
See what
with the backs?
Yeah,
E
Okay,
I'll tell you something
because
definitely
stop
a serum, not Shadow Kharja.
Looks like I was wrong about everything as usual.
Please use that second sight of yours.
I have to know what really happened.
I'm on it.
Mhm.
So much blood.
What are those?
Leather straps.
A lot of people died here.
A massacre?
Harmer straps cut with a knife in a rock with blood on it.
Please look like vanguard weapons.
There's no blood on them
versus men Didn't fight back.
Okay.
Oh,
those rocks shattered.
Mhm.
Something hit these stones something I've never seen before.
Things is Ercis helmet.
I thought she died in the field below, but must have been here.
All this trickery for what feels like it's just a torture.
Me.
I have a theory.
Yeah, but it takes a little imagination.
So far, your theories are better than other people's facts.
All right.
I think the s r um, ambushed Ursa and her men with a new weapon.
They mounted it on that tripod up there.
It fires waves of force.
Maybe sound.
Looks like it cracked the stone there.
I think it paralyzes people instead of killing them, it dropped the vanguard right there.
No blood on their weapons.
You'll fight.
But why paralyzed?
And if you're only gonna move them and got them?
They were trying to hide something.
Look here.
A bloody rock
that they used to smash her sis facing or someone else's.
Yeah, yeah.
Thes leather straps have been cut as if they took the armor off.
Someone that can't be.
Her body is lying in state in Meridian.
I saw it.
You said she was unrecognizable.
Maybe they switched another body into her armor.
Someone around the same size and mutilated it enough So it could have been anyone.
Even IRSA
go back to Meridian.
Take another look at that body If it's really IRSA, of course.
No longer.
But if I'm right,
then my sister could be alive.
I'm going meet me back there when you can.
Mhm
dawn Breaking every time is different.
When you came here Really
in the morning.
You mean
you
Mhm?
Uh huh.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Stocking up.
It's
uh huh.
I'll talk that a way.
Uh, okay.
Yeah,
yeah.
Uh huh.
Mhm.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Mhm.
Uh huh,
Yeah,
your country
and
oh,
yeah.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
In this country.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Drawing back
with the
okay,
It's
and
yeah,
okay.
Okay.
Worth watching?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Just
Yeah.
Oh,
your trash.
Now?
Yes.
Come on.
Hello.
Here we are.
That so
Thank you.
Right.
Are you actually e?
Yes.
Mhm
it
Really?
You know?
Yeah.
I want to thank
just
people
different.
Okay.
Wait.
Yeah.
Wow.
And
wow.
Yeah,
Turmeric.
Richard, Richard